A Guide to the Papers of Julian Bond, 1897-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series VII: Topical Files
  - Subseries A: General
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (9 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:4)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (10 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:5)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (11 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:6)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (1 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 103:7)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (2 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 103:8)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (3 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:1)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (4 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:2)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (5 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:3)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (6 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:4)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (7 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:5)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (8 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:6)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies (9 of 9 folders). (Box-folder 104:7)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- Correspondence about Government Agencies, 1980, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 104:8)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- Correspondence with Government Agencies, 1970, 1975 (Box-folder 104:9)
    - Freedom Summer and Freedom Schools, 1964, 1989, 1994 (Box-folder 105:1)
    - Gay Rights and Gay Marriage, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 105:2)
    - Greased Lightning Movie about Wendell Scott, the First Black Man to Compete on the Racing Circuit, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 105:3)
    - Hate Crime Definition, n.d. (Box-folder 105:4)
    - Hate Groups- Council of Conservative Citizens, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 105:5)
    - Hate Groups- White Supremacists Groups, ca. 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 105:6)
    - Health Care Disparities, 2004, n.d. (Box-folder 105:7)
    - Thomas Jefferson Democrat- Essay by Palmer Weber, ca. 1950 (Box-folder 105:8)
    - Kent State- Chronology of Events, 1996 (Box-folder 105:9)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr.- Miscellaneous Copies, etc., ca. 1955-1990 (Box-folder 105:10)
    - Preston King, 1999 (Box-folder 105:11)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 105:12)
    - Boyd Lewis, 1996 (Box-folder 105:13)
    - Lift Every Voice and Sing: 100 Years, 100 Voices Black National Anthem by James Weldon Johnson, 1999 (Box-folder 105:14)
    - Lowndes Development Corporation concerning a Civil Rights Trail in Alabama, 1992 (Box-folder 105:15)
    - Legacy of the 1960s Culture, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 106:1)
    - Lincoln University- Three Students Look at Lincoln in 1929- Paper by Langston Hughes, 1950 April (Box-folder 106:2)
    - Aaron McGruder's The Boondocks- NAACP Image Award and Condoleezza Rice, 2002 (Box-folder 106:3)
    - Media and the Civil Rights Movement- A National Symposium, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 106:4)
    - Media- America's Black Forum, 1980 (Box-folder 106:5)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Black Ethnic Memorabilia and Collectibles, ca. 1906-1997 (Box-folder 106:6)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Civil Rights Movement, 1947-1989 (Box-folder 106:7)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Civil Rights Movement, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 106:8)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Congressional Gold Medal Ceremony for President Nelson R. Mandela, 1998 (Box-folder 106:9)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Jazz, 1954-1956, 1960, With autographs. (Box-folder 106:10)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Jazz, 1988, 2004, n.d., With autographs. (Box-folder 106:11)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Leaders of the Civil Rights Movement- Funerals and Memorials, 1969-2002 (Box-folder 106:12)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Monticello and Thomas Jefferson, 1993, 2001 (Box-folder 107:1)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- National Election Campaigns, Virginia Governor Doug Wilder Inauguration, etc., 1972-1999 (Box-folder 107:2)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Nobel Prize Centennial Banquet and Award Ceremony, 2001 (Box-folder 107:3)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Political Figures, 1966-2001 (Box-folder 107:4)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- Presidential Inaugurations of William Jefferson Clinton, 1993, 1997 (Box-folder 107:5)
    - Memorabilia and Ephemera- VIP, 1988-2003 (Box-folder 107:6)
    - Mississippi Burning Film, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 107:7)
    - Mississippi State Sovereignty Commission, 1989, Copies from 1963-1965. (Box-folder 107:8)
    - Montgomery, Alabama, 1955-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 107:9)
    - Music, 1982, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 107:10)
    - Music- Civil Rights Movement, 1989, 2000 (Box-folder 107:11)
    - Music- Rock 'n Roll, 1949-1994 (Box-folder 107:12)
    - Music- Rock 'n Roll, 1995 (Box-folder 107:13)
    - Music- Rock 'n Roll, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 107:14)
    - National Army Surveillance, 1970, 1976 (Box-folder 108:1)
    - National Conference on Black Power, 1967 (Box-folder 108:2)
    - Oral History, 1991-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 108:3)
    - Presidential Election, 2004 (Box-folder 108:4)
    - Prison Reform and Louis Wolfson, 1971 (Box-folder 108:5)
    - Race, 1964-2002 (Box-folder 108:6)
    - Race, Crime and Poverty, 1903-1999, n.d., Some copies. (Box-folder 108:7)
    - Reconstruction, 1988 (Box-folder 108:8)
    - Religion, 1997-2005 (Box-folder 108:9)
    - Republican Party, 1968, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 108:10)
    - Resurrection City, n.d. (Box-folder 108:11)
    - School Desegregation, 1950-1967 (Box-folder 108:12)
    - School Vouchers, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 108:13)
    - Selma, Alabama, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 108:14)
    - The Sentencing Project/and Race and Criminal Justice, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 108:15)
    - Slavery and Reparations, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 108:16)
    - Social Security Center on Budget and Policy Priorities on African-Americans, Hispanic Americans and Social Security Reform, 1998, 2005 (Box-folder 109:1)
    - Southern League, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 109:2)
    - Surveys- National Opinion Polls conducted by the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies and Doble Research Associates, 1997, 2000 (Box-folder 109:3)
    - Surveys- Public Opinion on Race and Affirmative Action conducted by the National Opinion Research Center, 1996 (Box-folder 109:4)
    - Surveys- Racial Attitudes, Ethnic Images, Race Relations, conducted by the National Opinion Research Center, the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, Southern Regional Council and the Arthur Levitt Public Affairs Center at Hamilton College, 1990, 1997, 1999 (Box-folder 109:5)
    - Clarence Thomas Supreme Court Nomination- NAACP Report, 1991 August (Box-folder 109:6)
    - Clarence Thomas Supreme Court Nomination- Polls, 1991 (Box-folder 109:7)
    - Clarence Thomas Supreme Court Nomination- Reactions to his Nominations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 109:8)
    - United Nations- Julian Bond's Call to Action at the United Nations World Conference Against Racism concerning continued Racial Discrimination in the United States, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 109:9)
    - United Nations- Julian Bond's Call to Action at the United Nations World Conference Against Racism concerning continued Racial Discrimination in the United States- Research, 2000 (Box-folder 109:10)
    - University of Virginia, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 109:11)
    - Vietnam War, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 110:1)
    - Vietnam War- Research Material from Erich Martel, n.d. (Box-folder 110:2)
    - Voting- Increasing Black Participation, 2000 (Box-folder 110:3)
    - Voting- Population Characteristics, 1968-1970, 1984 (Box-folder 110:4)
  - Subseries B: Academic Course Evaluations and Lectures
    - Course Evaluations- The American University, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 110:5)
    - Course Evaluations- The American University, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 110:6)
    - Course Evaluations- The American University, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 110:7)
    - Course Evaluations- The American University, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 110:8)
    - Course Evaluations- Harvard University, 1991 (Box-folder 111:1)
    - Course Evaluations- The University of Virginia, 1995 (Box-folder 111:2)
    - Course Evaluations- The University of Virginia- History of the Civil Rights Movement, n.d. (Box-folder 111:3)
    - Course Evaluations- The University of Virginia- History of the Civil Rights Movement, n.d. (Box-folder 111:4)
    - Course Evaluations The University of Virginia The Sixties in Black and White, 2000-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 111:5)
    - Course Evaluations- Williams College, 1992 (Box-folder 111:6)
    - Course Outlines and Syllabi, 1988-2002, n.d. (Box-folder 111:7)
    - Course Reader- University of Virginia- Gonna Sit at the Welcome Table, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 111:8)
    - Course Research Material, 1988-2002 (Box-folder 111:9)
    - Course Research Material, n.d. (Box-folder 112:1)
    - Course Research Material, n.d. (Box-folder 112:2)
    - Lecture Notes, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 112:3)
    - Lecture Notes, n.d. (Box-folder 112:4)
    - Lecture Notes, n.d. (Box-folder 112:5)
    - Oral History Course- The American University, 1996 (Box-folder 112:6)
    - Oral History Project- The University of Virginia, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 112:7)
    - Project- Black Leadership- University of Virginia, 2000 (Box-folder 112:8)
    - Proposals- Teaching Civil Rights Movement History, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 112:9)
- Series VIII: Family and Personal Papers, including photographs
  - Subseries A: Julian Bond
    - Activities and Programs, 1956, 1966-1998 (Box-folder 113:1)
    - Activities and Programs, 2004 (Box-folder 113:2)
    - Activities and Programs, 2005, n.d. (Box-folder 113:3)
    - Address Book, n.d. (Box-folder 113:4)
    - Appointment Book, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 113:5)
    - Appointment Book, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 113:6)
    - Appointment Book, 1969 (Box-folder 113:7)
    - Appointment Book, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 113:8)
    - Appointment Book, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 113:9)
    - Appointment Book, 1970 (Box-folder 113:10)
    - Appointment Book, 1970 (Box-folder 113:11)
    - Appointment Book, 1971 (Box-folder 113:12)
    - Appointment Book, 1971 (Box-folder 113:13)
    - Appointment Book, 1972 (Box-folder 113:14)
    - Appointment Book, 1972 (Box-folder 113:15)
    - Appointment Book, 1973 (Box-folder 113:16)
    - Appointment Book, 1974 (Box-folder 114:1)
    - Appointment Book, 1975 (Box-folder 114:2)
    - Appointment Book, 1975 (Box-folder 114:2a)
    - Appointment Book, 1976 (Box-folder 114:3)
    - Appointment Book, 1977 (Box-folder 114:3a)
    - Artifacts and Memorabilia- Commemorative Coin honoring Martin Luther King, Jr., n.d. (Box-folder 114:4)
    - Artifacts and Memorabilia  Honorary Keys to Cincinnati, Ohio; Long Beach, California; New Orleans, Louisiana; Roanoke, Virginia; and Tulsa, Oklahoma, n.d. (Box-folder 114:5a-e)
    - Artifacts and Memorabilia- Political Buttons for Julian Bond; Portia; "EMK 1972"; SNCC; the 34 Ohio State students indicted in 1968, 1968-1972, n.d. (Box-folder 114:6)
    - Award of Merit for Service to Humanity- Bucknell University, 1998 May 23 (Box-folder 114:7)
    - Biographical Sketches of Julian Bond, 1968-75, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 115:1)
    - Birthday Salute from the NAACP given at the 93rd Annual NAACP Meeting, New York, New York (glass), 2002 (Box-folder 115:2)
    - Cartoon of Julian Bond inscribed by Bill Daniels, showing Bond knocking on the door of S.S. High with a "Different Point of View" brief case and the office occupant cowering under his desk, 1971 May 12, Oversize. (Box 115)
    - Certificates and Awards, 1968-2001 (Box-folder 115:3)
    - Certificates and Awards, 1968-2003, Oversize. (Box-folder 115)
    - Children, 1969, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 115:4)
    - Correspondence- Family and Personal, 1965-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 115:5)
    - Correspondence- Parents, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 115:6)
    - Drawing of Julian Bond by Solomon Sanders, 2004 (Box-folder 115:7)
    - Elementary School and George School, 1946-1957 (Box-folder 115:8)
    - Financia- Accountants, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 116:1)
    - Financial- Atlanta Transit Suit, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 116:2)
    - Financial- Dan Berstein, 1970 (Box-folder 116:3)
    - Financial- Black Audio Network, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 116:4)
    - Financial- Colossal Cattle Company, 1972-1973 June (Box-folder 116:5)
    - Financial- Colossal Cattle Company, 1973 July- December (Box-folder 116:6)
    - Financial- Colossal Cattle Company, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 116:7)
    - Financial- Earl Graves Publishing Company, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 116:8)
    - Financial- Frontiers Unlimited, Incorporated, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 116:9)
    - Financial- Georgia Legislative Retirement System, 1967 (Box-folder 116:10)
    - Financial- Hank Thomas Enterprises- Dairy Queen and Wishbone Franchises, 1969-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 116:11)
    - Financial- Hank Thomas Enterprises- Legal Matters, 1969, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 117:1)
    - Financial- Legal Investment Association, Inc., 1969 (Box-folder 117:2)
    - Financial- Los Angeles Times Syndicate, 1976 (Box-folder 117:3)
    - Financial- Motor Electronics, 1969 (Box-folder 117:4)
    - Financial- Mound Bayou Investment Corporation, 1967 (Box-folder 117:5)
    - Financial- Charles Negaro, et al., 1970-1974 (Box-folder 117:6)
    - Financial- Peanut Plantation, 1977 (Box-folder 117:7)
    - Financial- Robert P. Walker Enterprises, Ltd., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 117:8)
    - Financial- Touche Ross and Company, 1971, 1981-82, n.d. (Box-folder 117:9)
    - Financial- Leroy Wilson- Radio Series, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 117:10)
    - Financial- Wright, Jackson, Brown, Williams, Stephens, Incorporated, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 117:11)
    - Honorary Degree- Bates College, 1999 (Box-folder 117:12)
    - Honorary Degree- Berea College, 2004 (Box-folder 117:13)
    - Honorary Degree- The California State University, 1999 (Box-folder 117:14)
    - Honorary Degree- Dillard University, 1999 (Box-folder 117:15)
    - Honorary Degree- Edward Waters College, 19[?] (Box-folder 117:16)
    - Honorary Degree- Gonzaga University, 1998 (Box-folder 118:1)
    - Honorary Degree- Northeastern University, 1999 (Box-folder 118:2)
    - Honorary Degree- Ramapo College of New, 2002, 2 binders. (Box-folder 118:3-3a)
    - Honorary Degree- Williams, 2005 (Box-folder 118:4)
    - Honorary Degree- Washington University, St. Louis, 2000 (Box-folder 118:5)
    - Honorary Degree Plaque- Washington University, St. Louis, 2000 (Box-folder 118:6)
    - Legal, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 119:1)
    - Membership Cards, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 119:2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1977, 1991, n.d. (Box-folder 119:3)
    - Morehouse College Graduation, 1957-1971, 1996-98 (Box-folder 119:4)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond's Childhood and as Young Man, 1941-1963, n.d. (Box-folder 119:5)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond's Congressional Campaign, n.d. (Box-folder 119:6)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond's Congressional Campaign, n.d. (Box-folder 119:7)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Miscellaneous Campaigns, 1968-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 119:8)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond in the Georgia House of Representatives, ca. 1965-1975, 2 folders. (Box-folder 119:9-10)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond in the Georgia House of Representatives, with Pages, n.d. (Box-folder 119:11)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond in the Georgia Senate, n.d. (Box-folder 119:12)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond with a Group of Children on Stairs, n.d. (Box-folder 119:13)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond, 12 photographs mounted on boards, n.d., Oversize. (Box-folder 119)
      Including Julian Bond for Congress; a young Bond speaking from a podium outside; a large group photograph with Julian Bond, possibly the Georgia Legislature.
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- African Dance Ceremony, n.d., Oversize. (Box-folder 120)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Alone, ca. 1970-1990, n.d. (Box-folder 120:1)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Celebrities, 1972-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 120:2)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Civil Rights Leaders, ca. 1942-1989, n.d. (Box-folder 120:3)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Politicians, ca. 1957-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 120:4)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond on Saturday Night Live, with correspondence from 1978, 1977 (Box-folder 120:5)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Unidentified Groups and Individuals, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 120:6)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Public Appearances, 1971-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 120:7)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Public Appearances, n.d. (Box-folder 120:8)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Public Appearances- [Denver ?], n.d. (Box-folder 120:9)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Negatives and Contact Sheets, n.d. (Box-folder 120:10)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking at ASPA, n.d. (Box-folder 121:1)
    - Photographs  Julian Bond- Alabama State University WVAS and Friends of the Library, 1998 April 17, Oversize. (Box 121)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- America's Black Forum, n.d. (Box-folder 121:2)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- American Program Bureau Publicity Shots, n.d. (Box-folder 121:3)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Atlanta Sit-in Veterans, n.d. (Box-folder 121:4)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Awards and Honors, 1970-1998 (Box-folder 121:5)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking about Blacks and Southern Politics, n.d. (Box-folder 121:6)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Black Caucus (Georgia), n.d. (Box-folder 121:7)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- First Black Georgia House Members elected in the 20th Century, n.d. (Box-folder 121:8)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- College Speaker, 1968-1998 (Box-folder 121:9)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking to Community Relations Board, n.d. (Box-folder 121:10)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 121:11)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- James Forman Funeral Service, 2005 (Box-folder 121:12)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking at the Georgia Loyal Democrat Convention, 1972 (Box-folder 121:13)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Golden Monocle Club Member, 1973 (Box-folder 121:14)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Great March on Washington 25th Anniversary, 1988 (Box-folder 121:15)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Meeting with Martin Luther King, Jr. and Dedication of the King Portrait, n.d. (Box-folder 121:16)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking at the Kiwanis Club International Day Luncheon in Jamaica, 1969 (Box-folder 121:17)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Life Photograph Album with photographs removed from the album sheets, 1968, Oversize. (Box 121)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Meet the Press, 1998 (Box-folder 121:18)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Memphis Civil Rights Museum Dedication, 1992 (Box-folder 121:19)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Miscellaneous, including one with President Bill Clinton, 1999, n.d., Oversize. (Box-folder 121)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- NAACP Board Retreat and General, 1999-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 121:20)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- NAACP Honorees, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 121:21)
    - Photograph Albums- Julian Bond- NAACP Fight Against Apartheid in South Africa and Bond's Congressional Campaign from Susan Ross, 1985-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 121:22)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Narrating Scenes from the Series Rush Toward Freedom, n.d. (Box-folder 121:23)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Speaking at the National Press Club, 1998 (Box-folder 121:24)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- O'Keefe High School, n.d. (Box-folder 121:25)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- SNCC Conference, Hartford, Connecticut, 1988 (Box-folder 121:26)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- SNCC Reunion, 1988 (Box-folder 122:1)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- SNCC Conference, Raleigh, North Carolina, 2000 (Box-folder 122:2)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Southern Africa Conference, Lesotho, 1976 (Box-folder 122:3)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Southern Leadership Conference Alumni, 1990 (Box-folder 122:4)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Urban League Conference, 1975 (Box-folder 122:5)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Urban Revitalization Conference Press Conference, 1973 (Box-folder 122:6)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Voter Education Project, n.d. (Box-folder 122:7)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- WCAU Radio Interview, 1987 (Box-folder 122:8)
    - Photographs- Julian Bond- Wesley Community Centers, n.d. (Box-folder 122:9)
    - Photographs- Individuals- Identified, 1968-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 122:10)
    - Photographs- Pam [Horowitz ?] as a Child, and her parents, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 122:11)
    - Plaque from the Department of Transportation as a Civil Rights Activist, 1997 February 24 (Box-folder 122:12)
    - Plaque from the Port Arthur Branch NAACP, 1998 September 18 (Box-folder 122:13)
    - Plaque of 2001 Good Guy Award from the National Women's Political Caucus, 2001, Oversize. (Box 122)
    - Plaque from International Civil Rights Walk of Fame, 2004 September 14 (Box-folder 122:14)
    - Poems and Lyrics by Julian Bond, 1963-1977, 1990 (Box-folder 122:15)
    - Silhouette of Julian Bond, [1980?], Oversize. (Box 122)
    - Who's Who in the World Entry, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 122:16)
    - Horace J. Bond (1928-2000), 2000 (Box-folder 123:1)
  - Subseries B: Bond Family Papers
    - Horace Mann Bond (1904-1972)- Autobiography, n.d. (Box-folder 123:2)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Biographical Sketches, 1971-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 123:3)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Correspondence, 1933-1972, n.d. (Box-folder 123:4)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Correspondence, 1926-1948, Copies. (Box-folder 123:5)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Correspondence, 1951-1972 (Box-folder 123:6)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Legal, 1938, 1971 (Box-folder 123:7)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Lincoln University and Atlanta University, 1943-1961, n.d. (Box-folder 123:8)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Miscellaneous Papers, 1845-2000, n.d., Some copies. (Box-folder 123:9)
    - Horace Mann Bond- News clippings, 1924-1968 (Box-folder 123:10)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Papers at the University of Massachusetts, at Amherst, 1979, 1989 February-August (Box-folder 124:1)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Papers at the University of Massachusetts, at Amherst, 1989 September-1991 (Box-folder 124:2)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Papers at the University of Massachusetts, at Amherst- Guide, 1982 (Box-folder 124:3)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Photographs, n.d. (Box-folder 124:4)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Photographs of Rosenwald Schools in the South, ca. 1920-1935 (Box-folder 124:5)
    - Horace Mann Bond- UNESCO, 1948 (Box-folder 124:6)
    - Horace Mann Bond- Written Works, 1931-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 124:7)
    - The Rev. Dr. James Bond (1863-1929), 1901-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 124:8)
    - The Rev. Dr. James Bond (1863-1929)- Autobiography, 1970, n.d. (Box-folder 124:9)
    - J. Max Bond (1936 ?- ), 2004 (Box-folder 124:10)
    - Julia Bond (1908- )- Correspondence, 1931-1999, n.d., Some copies. (Box-folder 125:1)
    - Julia Bond- Music, Notes concerning, n.d. (Box-folder 125:2)
    - Julia Bond- Papers, 1925-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 125:3)